pdfoxy.com 2010-11-27

# Privacy Policy Free PDF Ebook Files Search and Download - PDFoxy.com

Cookies are pieces of information that a web site can transfer to an individual's web browser on their computer hard drive for record keeping when you visit such sites or blog. Cookies can make using web sites easier by storing information about your preferences on a particular website. The information remains on your computer after the Internet session finishes. 

PDFoxy cookies to improve the functionality of its site and support all browsers. PDFoxy uses cookies to assess the performance of the Website and to confirm your preferences.

Most Internet browsers are pre-set to accept cookies. If you prefer not to receive cookies, you can adjust your Internet browser to refuse cookies or to warn you when cookies are being used. These cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information. 

Your Internet Protocol ("IP") address is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet, like your Internet Service Provider, your company or your university. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, gather broad demographic information, and administer our website. 

To provide goods and services of interest to you, PDFoxy have relationships with other companies like Google (www.google.com/adsense), etc. that place ads on our web site. These companies may use information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information (NOT including your name, address, email address, or telephone number). This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing Beijing automotive ads to someone in Beijing, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

For further information, consult the privacy policy of each those web sites. Privacy Policy of Google is available at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>. While your individual information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use aggregated anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.

This web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by PDFoxy. Please be aware that we, PDFoxy, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

PDFoxy encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this web site.

Our sites utilize state-of-the-art security technology to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of such information. Nonetheless, we are not responsible for any breach of its security or for the actions of any third parties that may obtain any personal information.

PDFoxy.com offers its files search technology on an "as is" basis. PDFoxy.com distributes information supplied by third parties and provides Internet links and references gathered from outside sources.

We collect PDF files and ebooks from many web site for personal or educational purposes only. _Not for resale_. All PDF files and ebooks are the property of their respective owners. Please respect the publisher and the author for their creations if their books copyrighted. 

We are not responsible for PDF Files and ebooks that users have downloaded. We are not responsible for the use of PDF files and ebooks by the users after they downloaded them.

Due to the nature of the Internet, PDFoxy.com does not warrant that access to PDFoxy web sites or any of their pages will be uninterrupted or error free. PDFoxy does not warrant or make any representations regarding the usefulness of or the expected results of the material contained on PDFoxy web sites.
